<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="11C23437-C669-45D8-B3C6-A9C2EE5B7A79">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120925" date="2012-09-25 23:37:06 -0700"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;All Nighter&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Game Doc . . . </richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;EPROM&#x2019;s RobotSexTape and Bay Area EP are the perfect soundtrack to what I'm working on tonight. 7th dimensional rocket ships going up. DON'T SLEEP =) =) =)&#xD;&#xD;Here&#x2019;s a little sample, typos and all, because it&#x2019;s 3:17 in the morning, dammit, and I could fix typos or I could keep on going:&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;&#xD;&lt;/b&gt;Welcome to Indiex, located in the 7th dimension, whose life forms are dependent on a wide spectrum of sound waves for survival. The majority of Indiex native population are Deaddy Bears, a form of intelligence not found on Earth, whose lives and very biology are shaped by musical sound waves. In 7D, some concepts that are considered "abstract" on Earth are experienced as concrete realities. The Deaddy Bears' senses have evolved to be hyper aware of music sounds. In 7D, however, concepts such as tonality, key, Jazz, and Dubstep are experienced in physical forms. It is for this reason that Indiex is where rock stars go when they die, continuing to exist as physical manifestations of the sound waves with which their music and various aspects of their souls resonate. &#xD;&#xD;If you were to describe this world in terms of a Role Playing Game, you would only be telling half of the story. If you were to describe this world in terms of a Social Game, you would be missing the point. The mechanics of game play are embedded within the ark of the story and can be determined by how one chooses to play the game. On the other hand, even describing this world as a game would be inaccurate because its very existence is a concrete depiction of what is really happening right now in abstract terms. Just as scientific models are accepted metaphors that accurately describe observed phenomena, this "game" models phenomena of music and culture as they are currently understood. Unlike scientific models, the game is dynamic, by its very nature redefining itself in real time to reflect changes in the real world. Allow me to show you around a little bit. You will see what I mean.&#xD;&#xD;[walkthrough[&#xD;&#xD;Login Page&#xD;&#xD;	Have you been here before? &#xD;	&#xD;		If so, you log in and are taken to your last drop off...&#xD;&#xD;		If not, we will help get you there in the style and manner that best suit your budget, your dreams, and your current level of interest. There are several paid levels of gameplay which include various different amenities as well as one free entry level of 		gameplay.&#xD;&#xD;			At the premium level you are able to create a custom avatar that will be yours to play through and edit throughout your gaming experience. You will be able to communicate with other players at this level. You will be able to influence the game 			world in various ways when you play at this level, but more on that later.	&#xD;			For now, lets say you choose the free level of gameplay. All you must do is register and we will get you on your way. The includes basic information requests such as username, password, demographics, but it also includes more unusual 			information requests that begin to shape the narrative of the player. For example:&#xD;&#xD;				How did you get here? Please check all that apply.&#xD;&#xD;					A) I am a dead rock star&#xD;					B) I am a living rock star&#xD;					C) I am a devotee of a dead OR living rock star&#xD;					D) I am currently experiencing a psychotropic chemically induced state					E) I am just visiting&#xD;					F) Other, please specify: ____________________&#xD;&#xD;				&#xD;				Wonderful. Thank you for your response. A visitor access pass has been granted. &#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Friday, November 12, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="12_Game_Doc_._._._files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="300px" height="300px"/>
</content>
