<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RUCA’S BLOG</title>
    <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description>Free music, the world of games, &lt;br/&gt;the real lives of Ivan and Cecily</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <item>
      <title>Standing Out in the Electronic Crowd</title>
      <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2011/5/15_Standing_Out_in_the_Electronic_Crowd.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5dc1f30-5448-4547-903c-b8883e506e39</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2011 16:18:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2011/5/15_Standing_Out_in_the_Electronic_Crowd_files/IMG_0391_1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Media/object060.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:176px; height:132px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Check out this article from Little White Earbuds.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.littlewhiteearbuds.com/feature/everything-popular-is-wrong-making-it-in-electronic-music-despite-democratization/&quot;&gt;Everything popular is wrong: Making it in electronic music, despite democratization&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I read the article after transcribing a course on internet marketing for life coaches and was intrigued by how similar the challenges facing the coaches were to the those being faced by electronic musicians.</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2011/5/15_Standing_Out_in_the_Electronic_Crowd_files/IMG_0391_1.jpg" length="149633" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iron Butterflies: How Remarkable Women Lead</title>
      <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2011/2/17_Iron_Butterflies__How_Remarkable_Women_Lead.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b98eb7a-c044-415c-8dcd-4ee4f23068f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 11:55:14 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2011/2/17_Iron_Butterflies__How_Remarkable_Women_Lead_files/Photo%20on%202011-01-18%20at%2015.37%206-filtered.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Media/object061.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:176px; height:213px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Ever feel like you’re walking uphill both ways? I do... quite often. While the challenge itself makes me proud of the work I am doing, I take solace in the wise, encouraging words of women who have come before me. I’d like to thank Sheri Graner Ray for sending this article to the Women in Game Development mailing this. In the article, Dawn Reiss discusses some key points from Dr. Birute Regine’s book, Iron Butterflies: How Remarkable Women Lead. Here are Birute’s Four C’s to Becoming an Iron Butterfly. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;1.  Connect to Your Passion.&lt;br/&gt;A lot of people are doing work they aren’t passionate about. It’s important to connect with something you are passionate about even if it is as hobby.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;2.  Collaborate with Women as a Way of Healing.&lt;br/&gt;Collaboration enables you to compete. There is a lot of distrust among women, but instead of being worried about betrayal, try to trust. Successful influential women always have a large support network.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;3.  Recognize Feminine Power as a Collective Power&lt;br/&gt;“The world of collaboration is all new territory. That is what is Obama trying to do,” Regine says. “It requires a lot of self reflection, openness and it requires going beyond yourself. It is asking what is the common benefit for both of us? We are at a tipping point and moving from a domination-based society to a more collaborative one. There is the myth that you need to do it alone and be more effective.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;4.  Have a Sense of Community and Find the Connectors&lt;br/&gt;Know that you are part of a movement that is happening. On the average, most women are leading the way and often don’t realize they are part of something bigger. Most women show collaborative leadership. It is leadership that is done behind closed doors through mutual empowerment where there’s not a lot of chest pounding. It’s important for companies to find those connectors and start rewarding them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Check out the article by clicking this link: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.openforum.com/idea-hub/topics/lifestyle/article/iron-butterflies-how-remarkable-women-lead-dawn-reiss?cid=rs-gambd-2011Booming-Outbrain&quot;&gt;Iron Butterflies: How Remarkable Women Lead.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Stay strong, Butterflies!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2011/2/17_Iron_Butterflies__How_Remarkable_Women_Lead_files/Photo%20on%202011-01-18%20at%2015.37%206-filtered.jpg" length="50815" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.me.J Final Approach</title>
      <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2011/1/11_J.me.J_Final_Approach.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">392f8e67-d0c8-417b-8e35-13dc60d6a1f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 12:33:46 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Media/widget-snapshot_2.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:176px; height:147px;&quot;/&gt;Check out the youtube video for J.me.J’s song Final Approach my friend Ben Chaykin made =) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Music Promoters Calendar</title>
      <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2011/1/11_Seattle_Music_Promoters_Calendar.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92cb1694-b23d-4899-aaa6-a5c8cd97668a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2011 11:45:32 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>Share your events. List event date, location, artists booked, location, promoter contact info, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan 14 we’re all fucked</title>
      <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/29_Jan_14_were_all_fucked.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0257ea1d-b68d-40cb-8851-35ab192c5f6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 18:54:18 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/29_Jan_14_were_all_fucked_files/droppedImage-filtered.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Media/object062.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:176px; height:235px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Amy (aka Amalala on soundcloud)  just came over to plan her debut DJ set selecting as Diggaboo. She’s doing the set to open the upcoming Bil Bless show with roomy and half of Splatinum Andrew Luck. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;You heard it here first, people: Jan 14 Bil Bless, Andrew Luck feat selector Diggaboo at the Loft in Sodo (Seattle)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Listening to them plan the set now and daaaayum... .&lt;br/&gt;Their goal is to make people have sex on the dance floor. From the sound of it, we’re all fucked =)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://soundcloud.com/amalala&quot;&gt;Check out Amy’s soundcloud here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/29_Jan_14_were_all_fucked_files/droppedImage-filtered.jpg" length="72234" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splatinum Nondisclosure Agreement&#13;</title>
      <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/25_Splatinum_Nondisclosure_Agreement.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b178843f-a055-4bbc-a0fc-a1ce5cd52b74</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2010 15:09:31 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Media/widget-snapshot_3.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:176px; height:132px;&quot;/&gt;Merry Christmas! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I had to sign an NDA for my internship with Splatinum. Some of the details I can no longer disclose without consent include: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;-Who they have sex with&lt;br/&gt;-Technology&lt;br/&gt;-Coding&lt;br/&gt;-Concepts in general&lt;br/&gt;-Songs&lt;br/&gt;-Sample sources&lt;br/&gt;-Costumes&lt;br/&gt;-Costume sources&lt;br/&gt;-Kinks, fetishes, and fantasies&lt;br/&gt;-Familial relationships&lt;br/&gt;-Family recipes&lt;br/&gt;-Art&lt;br/&gt;-Things they say when they are drunk&lt;br/&gt;-Crying&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This is going to be awesome. I will share what I can.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lands an internship</title>
      <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/24_Lands_an_internship.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">984b135a-5d6d-4ccc-b785-c41f98bc43b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2010 14:09:45 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/24_Lands_an_internship_files/IMG_2430-filtered.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Media/object063.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:176px; height:132px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Remember this little gem? &lt;a href=&quot;http://ow.ly/3udQb&quot;&gt;http://ow.ly/3udQb&lt;/a&gt;  The gentlemen of Splatinum liked it so much that they offered me an internship. My title is Rich Media Marketing Producer. Task #1: Learn the Lemur... here we go =)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/24_Lands_an_internship_files/IMG_2430-filtered.jpg" length="109529" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe’s Crab Shack is dead to me</title>
      <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/19_Joes_Crab_Shack_is_dead_to_me.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d0fa3f9-5678-4f2c-8826-37ab1ea513e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2010 00:26:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/19_Joes_Crab_Shack_is_dead_to_me_files/ai_140-filtered.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Media/object064.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:176px; height:132px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;I can’t wait to play Heavy Rain. Rich narrative, complex characters, many paths... it sounds like just my type of thing, so I was intrigued by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.industrygamers.com/news/sony-missed-opportunity-to-market-heavy-rain-to-women-says-cliff-bleszinski&quot;&gt;this article&lt;/a&gt;. Heavy Rain is the kind of game women can fall in love with. I wonder, is it too late for Sony to get the memo?  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In other news, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamasutra.com/blogs/DariusKazemi/20090428/1274/Writing_a_Resume_for_a_Game_Company.php&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; is a very useful little Gamasutra article by Darius Kazemi I found on writing a resume for a game company, especially for college students or recent grads. Of course, the information applies to other industries as well. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Spoiler alert: Kazemi says to leave out that irrelevant and embarrassing _______ job that still gives you the occasional frustration nightmare. From now on, Joe’s Crab Shack is dead to me. Why did I ever wait so long?!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/19_Joes_Crab_Shack_is_dead_to_me_files/ai_140-filtered.jpg" length="5994" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$50,000 Women in Games Scholarship</title>
      <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/18_$50,000_Women_in_Games_Scholarship.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d586ebb-8af8-45e5-9a1a-01c5310822cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2010 19:54:56 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/18_$50,000_Women_in_Games_Scholarship_files/nickiposterarmflat.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Media/object065.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:176px; height:235px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;I found out about a thick, juicy scholarship for women in games from the Women In Games facebook page. Apparently it’s the first scholarship of its kind. Thank you, thank you, thank you to the Vancouver film school and all of the sponsors who made the scholarship possible. Even if I don’t win, I get teary thinking of the opportunities I want to create for other girls someday. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamedesignexpo.com/2010/12/announcing-100000-in-scholarships/&quot;&gt;Scholarship info here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Recommended listening: &lt;br/&gt;Nicki Minaj, “I’m the Best” from Pink Friday&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“I ain't gotta get a plaque I ain't gotta get awards&lt;br/&gt;I just walk up out the door&lt;br/&gt;All the girls will applaud All the girls will commend&lt;br/&gt;As long as they understand&lt;br/&gt;That I'm fighting for the girls never thought they can win&lt;br/&gt;Cause before they could begin you told them it was the end&lt;br/&gt;But I am here to reverse the curse that they live in&lt;br/&gt;Got two bones to pick ima only choose one&lt;br/&gt;You might get addressed on the second album&lt;br/&gt;Which means you can breathe till I mothafucken say so&lt;br/&gt;To all my bad bitches I could see your halo.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Feel me? Thanks, Nicki. Keep fightin.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/18_$50,000_Women_in_Games_Scholarship_files/nickiposterarmflat.jpg" length="143094" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes We Can</title>
      <link>http://www.cecilyismyruca.com/cecilyismyruca/Blog/Entries/2010/12/13_Yes_We_Can.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8926b237-d700-4e45-8ba5-941282debaef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 18:02:20 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>I’m really inspired by the young creator of &lt;a href=&quot;http://sizzleit.com/&quot;&gt;sizzleit.com&lt;/a&gt; who I read about in &lt;a href=&quot;http://finance.yahoo.com/news/No-Jobs-Young-Graduates-Make-nytimes-217264902.html?x=0&quot;&gt;this article&lt;/a&gt;. To some it up for you,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“FIVE years ago, after graduating from New York University with a film degree and thousands of dollars in student loans, Scott Gerber moved back in with his parents on Staten Island. He then took out more loans to start a new-media and technology company, but he didn’t have a clear market in mind; the company went belly up in 2006.&lt;br/&gt;“It made me feel demoralized and humiliated,” he says. “I wondered if this was really what post-collegiate life was supposed to be like. Did I do something wrong? The answers weren’t apparent to me.”&lt;br/&gt;Still in debt, Mr. Gerber considered his career options. His mother kept encouraging him to get a “real” job, the kind that comes with an office and a boss. But, using the last $700 in his bank account, he decided to start another company instead.&lt;br/&gt;With the new company, called &lt;a href=&quot;http://us.lrd.yahoo.com/SIG=10t1gipoc/**http%3A//www.sizzleit.com/&quot;&gt;Sizzle It&lt;/a&gt;, Mr. Gerber vowed to find a niche, reduce overhead and generally be more frugal. The company, which specializes in short promotional videos, was profitable the first year, he says.&lt;br/&gt;Mr. Gerber, now 27, isn’t a millionaire, but he’s paid off his loans and doesn’t have to live with his parents (he rents an apartment in Hoboken, N.J.). And he thinks his experience can help other young people who face a daunting unemployment rate.&lt;br/&gt;In October, Mr. Gerber started &lt;a href=&quot;http://us.lrd.yahoo.com/SIG=11dqsqqp9/**http%3A//www.nevergetarealjob.com/council/&quot;&gt;the Young Entrepreneur Council&lt;/a&gt; “to create a shift from a résumé-driven society to one where people create their own jobs,” he says. “The jobs are going to come from the entrepreneurial level.” ...&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;I just emailed them to ask how they think I can find music artists who want stop motion promotional videos like the one above that I just made for Moogy Bruise, aka Andrew Luck from Splatinum. I’ll let you know what they say!! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
