<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="11C23437-C669-45D8-B3C6-A9C2EE5B7A79">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20120925" date="2012-09-25 23:37:03 -0700"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Poor&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;deadmau5&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Poor deadmau5/the Third Summer of Love</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>This blog post made me sad, especially because it came from deadmau5.&#xD; &#xD;&lt;a href="http://choleric-mau5.blogspot.com/2010/10/raves.html"&gt;http://choleric-mau5.blogspot.com/2010/10/raves.html&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xD;I was recently in an argument about this to no avail. I&#x2019;m just gonna quote his whole post (his writing unedited, typos and all): &#xD;&#xD;&#x201C;Am i the only person in the world who cringes when they hear the word "rave"? As in, am i the only person to think that it's more or less been so shifted out of context of what the term meant to me back in 1995-1999? I don't know why it irritates me so much, maybe its just because "back in the day" i had something unique and special to me... and now it seems that it's for someone else, so i guess it would be like something taken from you and found and loved by someone else some many years later... like an ex or something.&#xD;&#xD;"Raves" to me have always been ... i guess, breaking into some basement in Kensington Market in Toronto back in 96... walking into an extremely dark / poorly lit network of cellars, of course puslating to the beat of whatever the flavor was at the time. Or possibly even hitting up the science center, for a more organized all nighter of complete and utter randomness and jungle.&#xD;&#xD;Or the News, Hullabaloo, Citrus, Dose, Phlux in NY... all that shit... i dont recall ever buying a ticket to any of these raves on ticketmaster.com, or buying merch and fucktons of 12$ bottles of water.&#xD;&#xD;it's just bizzare to me as to what passes off as raves these days... maybe this is one of those "hey im getting old rants" and i havent at all ruled out the idea that ... all this is definatley new to the younger generation of fun fur donning "ravers".. therefore its a big exciting thing for them... so why the hell get so depressed to hear about some kid who's been in "the scene" they call it, for no more than 36 minutes, telling me im not a part of it?&#xA0; Absolutley right though. most times, i dont feel a part of it, personally... if i can connect with it via my music, and vicariously be involved with the newer "scene" then great.... but i still have to think that it came and went for me.&#xD;&#xD;its pretty hard to explain.&#x201D;&#xD;&#xD;To the pearl clutchers out there who would agree, listen up. &#x201C;Real&#x201D; raves still happen. More than ever before. There are simply more commercial events going on in &#x201C;the scene&#x201D; now that electronic music has reached mainstream appeal. On the other hand, maybe you are too old. Maybe hanging around a bunch of young kids in the dark no longer appeals to you. That&#x2019;s cool. Just don&#x2019;t be surprised when someone calls bullshit if you complain that raves are a dead phenomenon. &#xD;&#xD;To me the &#x201C;raves are dead&#x201D; opinion sounds like saying hip hop died in &#x2019;97. Just because the good shit is underground, doesn&#x2019;t me it isn&#x2019;t real. No, it&#x2019;s not the same. Of course not. Evolution is the nature of the beast. One thing I have to say I really like about the commercial raves (or whatever I&#x2019;m supposed to call them) is that they allow for the funding of epic art projects that would be difficult to create otherwise. I&#x2019;d say deadmau5 mau5head unveiled at Coachella falls into that category. Reminds me of the Eric Hoffer quote, &#xD;&#xD;"Every great cause begins as a movement, becomes a business, and eventually degenerates into a racket."&#xD;&#xD;If you focus on the business and the racket, you might not see the movement keeping it alive. Computer Music Magazine recently had a special Make Dance Music issue that shed so much light on this topic for me. It walked through this history of electronic music and the rave scene from various perspectives. I&#x2019;m not being paid to say this. I really think its a must read, even if you already know your history. Here&#x2019;s a link to the issue: &#xD;&#xD;&lt;a href="http://www.musicradar.com/computermusic/make-dance-music-255576"&gt;http://www.musicradar.com/computermusic/make-dance-music-255576&lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xD;Two weeks ago I was at a crazy rave in a warehouse that was abandoned because of the shitty economy. I smiled thinking how everything has come full circle, how it all continues to grow and change. Like our Wigan brethren in the eighties, the ravers I know are deeply disturbed by the hate mongering that has become commonplace in our culture and they work consciously to create safe, positive environments for people to dance, party and worship the almighty DJ. &#xD;&#xD;deadmau5: if you&#x2019;re missing that old special feeling, come kick it with us sometime. You&#x2019;re always welcome. BIG UPS to the men and women who made it all possible. BIG UPS to all the people, from the promoters to the producers, from the DJs to the dancers, who continue to keep it alive today. Thank you, deadmau5. Fuckn Ghosts N Stuff always makes my day and your catalogue is to die for besides that. Thank you. Love you. Peace (:3 &#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>&lt;b&gt;Tuesday, October 12, 2010&lt;/b&gt;</richText>
  </textBox>
  <image id="generic-picture-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes" src="12_Poor_deadmau5_the_Third_Summer_of_Love_files/shapeimage_1.png" left="0px" top="0px" width="400px" height="300px"/>
</content>
